americasbest.com 2019-03-27

# Privacy Policy | America's Best Contacts & Eyeglasses

**Privacy Policy**  
Last Updated: 05.20.2017   
Welcome to the web site of America's Best Contacts & Eyeglasses ('America's Best', 'we', 'us', or 'our'). The following Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and share the information we receive about you or your device when you use our Web Site and associated mobile applications ('Web Site').  
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing and using our Web Site, you agree that you have read, understand and are bound by the terms and conditions set forth herein. The Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of our Terms of Use. As part of the Terms of Use, the Privacy Policy constitutes a legally binding agreement between you and us. The Terms of Use contain a binding arbitration agreement and class action waiver clause. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY PART OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR OUR TERMS OF USE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE SERVICES. You should review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. 

  * Personal Information Collected
  * Non-Personal Information Collected 
  * How We Use and Share Information
  * Your DITTO
  * Contests and Drawings
  * Links to Third Party Web Sites
  * Blog
  * Testimonials
  * Social Media Widgets
  * Prescription Verification
  * Security
  * Children's Policy
  * Updating Your Information
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * California Transparency in Supply Chains Act
  * California Proposition 65
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * Contact Us

**Personal Information Collected**

In general, you can use and visit our Web Site without submitting any personal information; however, in order to utilize and access certain features, you may need to submit your personal information. 'Personal information' refers to any information that you provide in connection with your use of our Web Site by which you can be personally identified. Personal information may include but is not limited to such things as your name, street address, telephone number, date of birth, e-mail address and any other information which might reasonably be used to identify you. We only obtain personal information from you when you submit it to us or provide it on our Web Site, which requires it in order to allow you to register, subscribe or take advantage of certain features, functions, services, activities, and promotions on our Web Site. America's Best collects information about its customers both during the order process and as customers navigate the Web Site. This information will be used to process your order and deliver it to you in a timely fashion.

For example, when you schedule an eye examination online, we ask for your name, date of birth, zip code, email address and telephone number in order to schedule the appointment with the store you choose to visit and contact you if we need to. If you choose to participate in our survey, you have the option of providing us with personal information such as your name, telephone number and email address so that we can respond to any complaints and improve your shopping experience. You also may choose to contact us regarding career opportunities, customer service issues or questions about this site, and America's Best will use your personal contact information (e.g., email address) to help respond and for customer service purposes. Please note that you may not be able to use some features and services of our Web Site if you choose not to provide your personal information when requested.

Top   

**Non-Personal Information Collected**

America's Best also routinely collects statistics from your browser or device on site usage patterns through web logs, web beacons and third party service providers. As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, device ID and type, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the operating system used by your device, date/time stamp, your mobile device's geographic location, and/or clickstream data. These statistics are not intended to relate to any particular individual. Instead, they are used internally to judge the effectiveness of Web Site features and content. Some real-time information is occasionally used to automatically suggest a product to a customer based on that customer's observed preferences.

When you visit or interact with our Web Site, we (or our third party service providers) may use cookies and other types of web technologies to collect technical and usage information. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our Web Site. When we link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our Web Site, we may use that information to send you offers online or through the mail.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use session ID cookies to allow visitors to easily navigate during checkout and access their account information. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We use a persistent cookie to welcome visitors returning to the site and to associate appropriate advertisements for our visitors.

Most Internet browsers allow you to disable, turn the cookie feature off, or reject cookies entirely by changing the settings on your Internet browser or clicking on the 'Help' link. Changing these settings may affect your ability to use certain features and functions of the Web Site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Web Site. Without a session ID cookie, your ability to complete a purchase and checkout will be limited.

If you are accessing our site on your mobile device, we may use mobile device IDs (the unique identifier assigned to a device by the manufacturer) or Advertising IDs (for iOS 6 and later), instead of cookies, to recognize you. We do this to store your preferences and track your use of our Web Site. Unlike cookies, device IDs cannot be deleted, but Advertising IDs can be reset in 'settings' on your iPhone.

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by us and our marketing partners, affiliates, analytics or online technical support providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We partner with a third party ad network to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by [clicking here.](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

You may interact with content on our Web Site through social media plugins provided by Facebook, Twitter, Google and LinkedIn. We do not control the information that these companies collect when you use their social media tools, whether through cookies or otherwise, nor do we control how these companies use any information they collect. We encourage you to review their privacy policies before interacting with our site through these social media tools. 

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

Top   

**How We Use and Share Information**  
When you schedule an appointment, we use the information you have provided to schedule your examination. The information you supply to us also is added to our customer database. You may receive periodic mailings, emails or telephone calls from us about new products and services, discounts, special promotions or upcoming events. We may also use your information to respond to your requests and inquiries, customize your user experience, prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities or other activities in violations of our Terms of Use and for any other purpose where you have provided your consent.   
The only America's Best employees with access to your information are those employees who need the information to do their jobs. All employees are educated about America's Best policies and practices in regard to safeguarding customer information, preventing its unauthorized access, use or disclosure and ensuring its proper handling.  
Our policy is that we will not sell or rent your personal information, unless you give us your consent or direct us to do so. We may, however, share the information we collect about you in limited circumstances including:

  * With third-party service providers who provide services related to your order. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.  Examples of these third-party service providers include a credit card processing company, a contact lens supplier, or a shipping service.
  * In accordance with our HIPAA Notice of Privacy Practices. With law enforcement agencies, governmental officials or other third parties as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web Site.
  * If we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to: prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss to us; prevent or report suspected illegal activity; protect anyone's rights, property, or safety; or enforce our Terms of Use.
  * With other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity or in connection with a partial or total sale of assets, bankruptcy proceedings, or similar legal process or corporate change.
  * When you otherwise consent or direct us to share your information with third parties.

Top

**Your DITTO**  
**How Virtual Try-on (DITTO) Works.** Your DITTO is a scan of your facial image and its unique proportions.    
**What We Collect With Your DITTO** :  We collect your DITTO and some basic identifying information you provide to us.   
**How We Use Your DITTO Image** :  Using your DITTO, we can show you how different styles of eyeglasses will look on your face and recommend additional styles through our website, periodic emails and direct communications to you. We may use non-identifiable information from your DITTO to improve our internal virtual fitting technology.   
**How Long We Keep Your Ditto** :  It is our policy to retain your DITTO no longer than three (3) years after your last interaction with us.  When that time period has elapsed, we permanently destroy your DITTO.

Top  

**Contests and Drawings**  
America's Best may sponsor or host contests or drawings from time to time. Some contests may be offered in conjunction with a third party sponsor and Web Site users will be notified at the time of the contest as to whether a third party sponsor is involved and whether the third party will be receiving the user's personal information to send promotional communications. The Web Site user can then choose whether to enter the contest or not at that time based on the terms and conditions associated with that particular contest.

Top   

**Links to Third Party Web Sites**

Our Web Site may include links to other web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of America's Best. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. Please be aware that we do not endorse and are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other web sites, and the Privacy Policy presented here does not apply to such third party web sites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any web site you visit.

Top

**Blog**  
Our Web Site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [service@americasbest.com](mailto:service@americasbest.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

Top

**Testimonials** ****  
We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you may contact us at [service@americasbest.com](mailto:service@americasbest.com).

Top  

**Social Media Widgets**  
Our Web Site includes social media features, such as the Facebook 'Like' button, and widgets, such as the 'share This' button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Web Site. These features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our Web Site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Web Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

Top

**Prescription Verification**  
America's Best may verify your prescription information provided with your order with your doctor or eye-care provider as required by Federal Law. For more information about how your Personal Health Information is protected, please see our HIPAA Notice.

Top   

**Security**

America's Best is committed to doing its best to maintain the security of all information collected on our Web Site. All transactions occur through our secure server, protected by a DigiCert® Secure Site Certificate. That means that we use encryption to secure information sent from your computer to our servers. In addition, credit card numbers and other sensitive information are encrypted in our database(s) to provide a second layer of security for your private information. When credit card information is transmitted online, America's Best uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) server software to prevent unauthorized access to the information. SSL is a highly sophisticated method of scrambling data as it travels from your computer to our Web Site's servers. You can identify the secure connection by looking for a locked padlock icon at the lower portion of your browser window.

We use commercially reasonable methods to prevent the unauthorized use, access, or disclosure of your personal information. While we strive to protect your personal information, no system can ever be 100% secure and we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your personal information. By using our Web Site, you are agreeing to assume this risk and any and all responsibility and liability that may arise. This assumption of risk and liability does not apply to New Jersey residents.

Top   

**Children's Policy**  
Our Web Site and its services are not directed to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children. It is our policy not to knowingly solicit or permit children under the age of 13 to provide their personal information for any purpose. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, if a person under age 13 submits information to us through any part of our Web Site, and we know that the person submitting information is under age 13, we will not use it for any purpose. We will delete the information as soon as we discover it, and we will not disclose it to third parties. If you are under the age of 13, please stop using our Web Site and its services.

Top   

**Updating Your Information**  
If you ever need to update or delete any information on file with America's Best, you may call us at 1-800-999-4758 or email us at [service@americasbest.com](mailto:service@americasbest.com). If you need to update your information when re-ordering, you will have a chance to make changes to your payment information, shipping and billing address(es) at checkout.

Top  

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California law permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared such information in the immediately preceding calendar year. At this time, America's Best does not disclose your personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes, only to assist America's Best in its own marketing efforts, so this requirement does not apply to us.

In addition, under California law, web site operators are required to disclose how they respond to web browser 'do not track' signals or other similar mechanisms that provide consumers with the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personal information of a consumer over time and across third party web sites, to the extent the operator engages in that collection. America's Best does not respond to any such 'do not track' signals, as no one do not track standard has gained consensus.

This law also requires web site operators to disclose whether third parties may collect personal information about their users' online activities over time and across different web sites when the users use the operator's web site. America's Best does not knowingly permit third parties to collect personal information about an individual consumer's online activities over time and across different web sites when a consumer uses our Web Site.

Third parties that have content embedded on our Web Site (such as social networking features) may set cookies on a user's browser and/or obtain information about the fact that a web browser visited our Web Site from a certain IP address. These third parties cannot collect any other personal information from our Web Site unless you provide it to them directly.

Top

**California Transparency in Supply Chains Act**

The California Transparency in Supply Chains Act of 2010 requires that applicable manufacturers and retailers such as National Vision, Inc. ('NVI') disclose their efforts to eradicate slavery and human trafficking from the supply chain.

NVI is committed to conducting business in accordance with ethical, legal and socially responsible rules and principles. These standards and commitments are outlined in the Company's Code of Conduct (the 'Code') which every NVI Associate is trained on upon hire and is distributed annually during the course of their employment. Consistent with the Code, we respect the personal dignity of every individual and comply with all applicable human rights laws. Failure to comply with the standards of the Code subjects violators, regardless of position, to disciplinary action up to and including termination of employment.

With respect to our supply chain partners, we expect the same commitment to high ethical standards and compliance with applicable laws, as detailed in the Code. NVI monitors the standards of our supply chain partners for quality, safety and employment standards by conducting annual scheduled on-site audits of our major vendors and laboratory manufacturers. When entering into written contracts with suppliers, NVI requires suppliers to comply with all applicable laws which include those that prohibit slavery and human trafficking. Failure to comply with all applicable laws subjects supplier to breach and possible termination of contract.

At this time NVI does not engage independent auditors or require separate verifications/certifications from its suppliers relating to human trafficking and slavery. While NVI believes it conducts its business with suppliers that maintain high ethical standards, we are continuously evaluating additional programs as it relates to combating the tragedy of human trafficking and slavery.

Top  

**California Proposition 65**

Attention California Residents:

Warning:   
California's Proposition 65 Warning: Eyewear products sold on this website contain chemicals known to the State of California to cause cancer, birth defects and other reproductive harm. For additional information please reference the California Office of Environmental Health Hazard Assessment (OEHHA) website at: <http://oehha.ca.gov/prop65.html>

Top  

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we decide to materially change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice of those changes on the Web Site and update the 'Last Updated' date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Web Site following the posting of revised Privacy Policy means that you accept and agree to the changes.

Top   

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [service@americasbest.com](mailto:service@americasbest.com), call us at **1-800-999-4758** , or send a written request to:

**_ALL OTHER PRIVACY POLICY QUESTIONS_**  
America's Best Contacts & Eyeglasses  
Corporate Headquarters  
2345 Commerce Ave, Building 2200  
Duluth, GA 30096 USA

**_FOR ONLINE ORDERS_**  
America's Best Contacts & Eyeglasses  
Online Contact Lens Orders  
4265 Diplomacy Dr   
Columbus, OH  43228 USA 

Top
